Friedlander, Walter A.; Papers ger003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence files, 1918-1984; 2; 3,383 folders
  - Professional correspondence, 1933-1984; 2.2; 1391 folders containing approx. 21,788 items of correspondence
    - Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, including some with former students), 1933-1984; 2.2.2; 1043 folders containing approx. 6835 items of correspondence
      - Rowan, Joseph, 1963-1965 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 826)
      - Rubin, Arnold P., 1979 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 827)
      - Rubin, Augusta, 1964-1978; Undated (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 828)
      - Rückmann, Christa, 1952-1953 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 829)
      - Rürup, Reinhard, 1977-1979 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 830)
      - Runkel, Erna, 1951-1962 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 831)
      - Ruppelt, Hans, 1978 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 832)
      - Russ, Georg, 1934; 1939 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 833)
      - Ruybalid, Louis A., 1970 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 834)
      - S., Carley, 1951-1952 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 835)
      - Sachs, Emmy, 1973; 1978 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 836)
      - Sachße, Christoph, 1979-1980 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 837)
      - Sailer, Erna, 1954-1957 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 838)
      - Salzberger, Georg, 1949-1972 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 839)
        Salzberger, Charlotte, 1972, 1980.
      - * Salzberger, Isca
      - Sand, René, 1933; 1953 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 840)
      - Sander, W., 1937 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 841)
      - Sanders, Daniel S., 1975-1984 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 842)
      - Sandvoß, Rainer, 1983 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 843)
      - Sapper, Harry J., 1952-1957 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 844)
      - Sato, Masayuki, 1980 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 845)
      - Sayre, John Nevin, 1965 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 846)
      - Schäfer, Dieter, 1976-1979 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 847)
      - Schäfers, Josef, 1972-1978 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 848)
      - * Schafer, Stephen
      - Schalit, Edith Feilchenfeld, 1954 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 849)
      - Schanzenbach, Marta, 1973-1984 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 850)
      - Schauwecker, Hans-Hermann, 1962-1978 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 851)
        Schauwecker, Ellen.
      - Schellenberg, Ernst, 1954-1966 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 852)
      - Schellhorn, Walter (Deutsche Verein für öffentliche Fürsorge), 1974-1976 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 853)
      - Schemm, Elizabeth (Bettie), 1957-1970; Undated (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 854)
      - Scherpner, Hans, 1954 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 855)
      - Schie, Gerhard, 1973-1981 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 856)
      - Schiefer, Jakob, 1966 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 857)
      - Schilling, Johannes, 1983-1984 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 858)
      - Schilling, K. G., 1974-1975 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 859)
      - Schindler, Julius, 1934-1940 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 860)
      - Schindler, Ruben, 1982-1983 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 861)
      - Schindler-Rainman, Eva, 1965-1981 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 862)
      - Schlingmann, Wilhelm, 1966-1967 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 863)
      - Schmitt, Harriet Polt, 1978 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 864)
      - Schnur, Alfred, ca. 1964 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 865)
      - Schocken, Dora, 1943-1979 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 866)
      - Schocken, Theodore, 1973 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 867)
      - Schonfield, Hugh J., 1983 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 868)
      - Schreiber, Adele, 1933 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 869)
      - Schreiber, Franz, 1948 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 870)
      - Schrekinger, Albert, 1949-1963 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 871)
      - Schröter, Richard, 1951 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 872)
      - * Schroetter, Erich von
        See German-American League for Culture, Chicago/ Deutschamerikanischer Kulturverband, Chicago
      - Schubert, Hermann, 1952-1964 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 873)
      - Schubert, Kurt, 1983 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 874)
      - Schubert, Margaret, 1979-1983 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 875)
      - Schuchardt, Irmgard, 1965-1974 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 876)
      - Schüpp, Dieter, 1980 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 877)
      - Schütz, José, 1933 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 878)
      - Schwabacher, Elsbeth, 1951-1976 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 879)
        Schwabacher, Albert.
      - Schwarz, Olga (Olly), 1940-1958 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 880)
      - Schwegler, Josef, 1933-1934 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 881)
      - Schwerin, Kurt, 1980 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 882)
      - * Scott, W. Richard
      - Segalman, Ralph, 1977 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 883)
      - Segner, Elfriede, 1983 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 884)
      - Seidel, Eva, 1961-1963 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 885)
      - Seidler, Horst, 1981 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 886)
      - Selby, Margery, 1971-1979 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 887)
      - Selden, Jean, 1950-1957 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 888)
      - Selig, Jules, 1954-1978 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 889)
        Selig, Christl.
      - Selver, Heinrich (Henry), 1933-1957 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 890)
        Selver, Irmgard, 1958.
      - Severence, Sally, 1946-1984 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 891)
        Severence, Howard M.
      - Seymour, Helen, 1958-1962 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 892)
      - Shaffer, Alice, ca. 1939-1960 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 893)
      - * Shrager, Jules
      - Silberstein, Ernst, 1937-1961 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 894)
      - Silver, Joseph R., 1967-1970 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 895)
      - Simmel, Hertha, 1938-1945 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 896)
        Simmel, Ernst.
      - Simon, Ellen, 1953-1982 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 897)
      - Simon, Elisabeth, 1978 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 898)
      - Simon, Herbert, 1955-1957 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 899)
      - Simon, Leo, 1934 (Box 19 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 900)
      - Simons, Savilla, 1953-1971; 1983 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 901)
      - Singh, Gurdip, 1965-1966 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 902)
      - Siporan, Max, 1983 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 903)
      - Skiba, Ernst-Günther, 1962-1971; 1978 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 904)
      - Small, F., 1933; 1965 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 905)
      - * Smigel, Erwin
        See Social Problems.
      - Smith, Rennie (Friends of Europe), 1933-1951 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 906)
        Smith, Lotte.
      - * Snyder, Charles R.
      - Solis, Joseph H., 1972 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 907)
      - Solmitz, Karoline, 1939; 1963 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 908)
      - Souhami, Herta, 1960-1961 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 909)
      - Specht, Harry, 1968-1983 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 910)
      - Spencer, Esther, ca. 1963-1964 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 911)
      - Spindler, Lore, 1953-1957 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 912)
      - Spiro, Shimon, 1976-1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 913)
      - Srivastava, Ram Gopal, 1962-1963 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 914)
      - Staniford, Edward F. (Ted), 1954-1974 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 915)
      - Staudinger, Hans, 1939 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 916)
        Staudinger, Else.
      - Steen, J. J., 1937-1938 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 917)
      - Stein, Herman D., 1954-1983 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 918)
      - Stein, Werner, 1965-1975 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 919)
      - * Steinitz, Hans
        See Aufbau (NY).
      - Steinthal, Eva, 1933; 1958 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 920)
      - Stephenson, E. P. (Red; Neighborhood House), 1956-1983 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 921)
        Stephenson, Madeleine.
      - Stern, Alfred P., 1945-1970 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 922)
        Stern, Ilse.
      - Stettner, Heinrich, 1959-1967 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 923)
        See also Hermann Luchterhand Verlag.
      - Stevenson, William (Bill), 1975-1984 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 924)
        Stevenson, Maria.
      - Steward, Newell, 1963 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 925)
      - Stewart, Katherine (Kay), 1952-1984 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 926)
      - Stoecker, Helene, 1941 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 927)
      - Stone, Olive, 1965-1971 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 928)
      - Strohm, Theodor, 1966 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 929)
      - Struß, Elisabeth, 1952-1953 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 930)
      - Stürzbecher, Manfred, 1979 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 931)
      - Sturm, Jean, 1946-1947; 1964-1973 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 932)
      - Sutton, Genevieve Mazo, 1950-1984 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 933)
      - * Taber, Merlin
      - Taggert, Kay, 1948-1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 934)
      - Taub, Siegfried, 1941-1944 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 935)
        Taub, Elsa.
      - Teichler, Helene, 1949; 1961 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 936)
      - tenBroek, Jacobus, 1965-1966 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 937)
      - Thalheim, Karl, ca. 1957 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 938)
      - Themal, Vera, 1980 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 939)
      - Thiele, Else, 1953-1955 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 940)
      - Theile, Gertrud, 1951-1983 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 941)
        Theile, Theodor, 1951-1972.
      - Thiruvady, Shrimati Chellamana, 1965-1980 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 942)
      - Thomas, Alexander, 1980 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 943)
      - Thomas, Cecil A., 1953-1963 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 944)
        Thomas, Fran, 1953-1970.
      - Thormann, Werner, 1934 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 945)
      - Thorun, Walter, 1960; 1963 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 946)
      - Thurman, Ernestine B., 1953 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 947)
      - * Tibbetts, Clark
      - Tichauer, Erna, 1934-1938 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 948)
        Tichauer, Théodore.
      - Tiedt, Friedemann, 1979 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 949)
      - Tikijian, Madeline, 1951-1952 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 950)
      - Titmuss, Richard, 1962-1971 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 951)
        Titmuss, Kay, 1973-1982.
      - Trenk-Hinterberger, Peter, 1978-1981 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 952)
      - Trinchero, Agnes, 1961-1966 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 953)
      - Triseliotis, John P., 1980 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 954)
      - Tsao, P.L. (The Free China Relief Association), 1964-1984 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 955)
      - Tulatz, Herbert A., 1962-1979 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 956)
      - Turner, Dorothy, 1972-1983 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 957)
      - Turnowsky(-Pinner), Margaret, 1961 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 958)
      - Uelzen, E. K., 1947 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 959)
      - Ury, Augusta Rubin, 1952-1960 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 960)
      - Vakharia, Parin, 1956-1962 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 961)
      - * Vakil, Radha
        See Patel, Radha.
      - VanDePol, Ann, 1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 962)
      - van Oordt, Toot Bleuland, 1934-1940 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 963)
      - Van Veen, Bernard, 1964-1972 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 964)
      - Vasey, Wayne, 1952-1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 965)
      - Vasudevaraju, V. A., 1979 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 966)
      - Viénot, Pierre, 1933 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 967)
        Viénot, Andrée.
      - Vinter, Robert D., 1964 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 968)
      - Vitt, Walter, 1979 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 969)
      - Vöhringer, Norbert, 1977 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 970)
      - Vogel, Rolf (Deutschland-Berichte), 1965-1976 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 971)
      - Volbach, Walter, 1939-1940 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 972)
      - Volkmar, M., 1955 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 973)
      - Wade, Alan D., 1971-1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 974)
      - Wagatsuma, Hiroshi, 1960-1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 975)
      - Waldman, Morris D., 1934 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 976)
      - Walker, William (Bill), 1965-1967; 1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 977)
      - Wallerstein, Judith S., 1972-1976 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 978)
        Wallerstein, Robert.
      - Walter, Hilde, 1934-1937 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 979)
      - Wander, Otto, 1937-1971 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 980)
        Wander, Bertha.
      - Wanetick, Fay J., 1979 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 981)
      - Wardell, Winifred, 1947-1960 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 982)
      - Warren, Roland L., 1965; 1973 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 983)
      - Watson, Elizabeth, 1956-1957; 1981 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 984)
      - * Watson, Patricia C.
      - Webb, Katherine, 1954 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 985)
      - Weber, Bernhard, 1974-1975 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 986)
      - Weber, Georg, 1967-1977 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 987)
      - Webler, Heinrich, 1975 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 988)
      - Wechsler, Hilde, 1968-1976 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 989)
      - Wee, Ann, 1970 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 990)
      - Weigert, Hans W., 1950 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 991)
      - Weinschenk, Klaus, 1978-1979 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 992)
      - Weisner, Stanley, 1974-1981 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 993)
      - Weiss, Peter, 1976-1978 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 994)
      - Wenzel, Gerd, 1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 995)
      - Wenzel, Irmela, 1960-1964 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 996)
      - West, Peggy, 1980-1984 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 997)
      - Westheimer, Ruth, 1976 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 998)
      - Westhoff, Winifred, 1974 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 999)
      - * Wheeler, Stanton
      - White, Carolyn, 1975-1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1000)
        White, Ralph.
      - White, Leslie (Forum for Contemporary History), 1973 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1001)
      - Wickert, Christl, 1982-1984 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1002)
      - Wieler, Joachim, 1975-1983 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1003)
      - Wiener, Alfred, 1960 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1004)
      - Wiener, Jack, 1961-1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1005)
      - Wilcox, Mark, 1963 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1006)
      - Wildman, Leo, 1977 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1007)
      - Wilensky, Hal, 1972-1976 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1008)
      - Wilker, Karl, 1965-1978 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1009)
      - Williams, Paula, 1977-1978 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1010)
      - Williams, Robinson, 1953-1962 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1011)
        Williams, Billie.
      - Wilson, Gertrude, 1964-1980 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1012)
      - Wilson, Joe H. R., 1981-1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1013)
      - Wilson, Louise A., 1965 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1014)
      - Wilson, Meredith, 1963 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1015)
      - Wilson, Suzanne, 1971-1972 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1016)
      - Wiltse, Kermit, 1963-1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1017)
      - Wimmer, Hein, 1953-1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1018)
        Wimmer, Trude.
      - Windesheim, Hans, 1961-1982 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1019)
      - Winkler, Heinrich August, 1976 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1020)
      - Wissell, Rudolf, 1948-1962 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1021)
      - Witsch, Werner, 1977-1978 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1022)
      - Witte, Ernest F., 1948-1977 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1023)
      - Wittelshoefer, Fritz, 1952-1957 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1024)
        Wittelshoefer, Lotte.
      - Wolff, Fritz, 1935-1936 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1025)
      - Wolff, Ida, 1953-1964 (Box 20 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 1026)